FRANKLIN DECKER

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER



Thailand, Chiang Mai



frank@franklindecker.com



Consultant, Accomplished Software Architect, Software engineer, Creative Web Developer, Designer and Technology Enthusiast, I have been working with various startups for 12+ years. I fulfil the roles of Team Lead and Product Owner. I enjoy product- and business-oriented work to produce successful software. I am happy to fill different roles on demand to help the team and product.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FPI, Inc.

Aug 2021 - Present Florida

SOFTWARE ARCHITECT

- Lead communication across multiple teams on three continents.
- Spearheaded softare integration with several partners.
- Archtected and designed all software communication channels.

AgentQuote.com, Inc.

Jun 2012 - Jul 2021 Fullerton

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- Conceptualizing and developed libraries to reduce additional costs involved in using thirdparty services.
- Developing client-side libraries to enable usage of the offline sync feature for insurance applications.
- Architected and designed insurance quote engine.
- Developing marketing platform with integration into 3rd-party APIs.
- Architected and designed various quote widgets.

National Access,

Inc.

La Habra

SENIOR DEVELOPER

- Architect and plan new client features into function server-side PHP/C# code
- Product owner
- Team lead for software team

Exodus 6 Studios, Inc

Jan 2009 - Mar 2010 Buena Park

CREATIVE WEB DEVELOPER

- Improving interface design, and usability
- Developing multiple constituent websites for various clients.
- Served as techincal liason between clients and managers for website issues and requests.

EDUCATION

Diablo Valley College

2011

ASSOCIATE OF SCIENCE

Department of Computer Science

SKILLS

VueJS

A React

PHP

Git Adobe Creative Suite

HTML5 CSS 3.0

Laravel 5+ WordPress

jQuery, Ajax Vultr, AWS, Linux, MacOS